Guide to the Alfred Tennyson Collection
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Purchase from Colonel E. S. M. Prinsep, 1775-1929; Series I; 3.6; (9 boxes)
  - WRITINGS
    - Tennyson, Alfred
      - "Queen Mary," galley proof of a portion of Act IV, Scene 3, with autograph manuscript corrections, n.d.
        Two copies
        See: Oversize, box 14, folder 453
      - "Queen Mary," page proofs of parts of Scene 5 & 6, Act III, with autograph manuscript corrections, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 315)
      - "Robin Hood"
        See: "The Foresters", Box 5, folder 301
      - "Sir John Franklin," autograph manuscript in Hallam Tennyson's hand (Box 5, Folder 316)
        On same page as "To Princess Frederica on her Marriage"
      - "The Song of the Wrens"
        See: "The Window", Box 5, folder 322
      - "Steersman, be not precipitate in this act," first ine of a 7 line poem addressed to W. E. Gladstone, 1884 (Box 5, Folder 317)
        A "final version" of lines 3-5 is written at the bottom of the page in Hallam Tennyson's hand
      - "To the Queen," page proof with autograph manuscript corrections, [1851?] (Box 5, Folder 318)
      - "To Alfred Tennyson, my grandson," autograph manuscript poem in four versions (of 2, 4, 3, and 7 lines), [1880?] (Box 5, Folder 319)
      - "To Princess Frederica on her Marriage," autograph manuscript poem of four lines, [1880?]
        The title is in Hallam Tennyson's hand. Written on the same page as "Sir John Franklin," in Hallam Tennyson's hand.
        See: "Sir John Franklin"
      - "To the Queen 1837," manuscript poem in the hand of Hallam Tennyson (Box 5, Folder 320)
      - "The Wanderer," autograph manuscript poem (Box 5, Folder 321)
      - "The Window," autograph manuscript, [1867?] (Box 5, Folder 322)
        Four Sections of the song cycle: No answer, ("The mist and the rain...") three 6-line stanza, with a fourth cancelled stanza; No answer, ("Winds are loud...") 9-line stanza, with two additional cancelled versions, both of 12 lines; The Answer, a 10 line stanza, with two additional cancelled versions of 10 lines and one other very different version (Beginning "Rosebud on her seal") with 16 lines, also cancelled; Ay, an 18-line stanza, with an additional cancelled version with the same number of lines
    - Tennyson, Hallam
      - See also: Tennyson, Mary Emily Prinsep, Box 6, folder 333
      - Materials for a Life of A.T. with annotations in the hand of Mary Emily Prinsep Hichens Tennyson (Box 5, Folder 323-329)
        Many pages are missing; approximately one-fourth of v.1 and one-half of v.2 are present. These privately printed volumes represent source material for the two volume Alfred Lord Tennyson: A Memoir, published in 1897. Laid in are scraps of other pages; a few notes in the hand of Mary Emily Prinsep Hichens Tennyson; several title-pages and some scattered pages annotated in the hand of Hallam Tennyson; and a manuscript account of the Cambridge Apostles in the hand of Douglas Devon Heath
    - Tennyson, Emily Sellwood
      - Diary: autograph manuscript of two pages, one describing the christening of Hallam Tennyson, 1852, 1854 (Box 5, Folder 330)
        A note in Mary Emily Prinsep Hichens Tennyson's hand is pasted on the manuscript. Removed from Hallam Tennyson's Memoir, vol. I
      - "Gordon Boys' Hymns": two poems (a morning and an evening hymn) each in eight verses (Box 5, Folder 331)
        Morning hymn copied in Hallam Tennyson's hand; evening hymn written in Emily Sellwood Tennyson's hand; pencilled note in Hallam Tennyson's hand: "Hymns by Emily Tennyson"
      - "Hands all round, a national song," page proof of poem in musical setting by Emily Sellwood Tennyson with a few pencilled corrections by Hallam Tennyson (Box 5, Folder 332)
    - Other Tennyson Family
      Tennyson, Frederick
      - "Daphne and other Poems": page proofs with autograph ms corrections, 1891
        Note on flyleaf: "Original proofs with F. T.'s corrections. Hallam Tennyson July 1891." Pasted inside front cover is an ALS (draft) from Alfred Tennyson to Algernon Charles Swinburne dated Aug 1891[?]
      - Tennyson, Mary Emily Prinsep
        - Alphabetical index, with notes, to Hallam Tennyson's Alfred Tennyson: A Memoir (Box 6, Folder 333)
          A list of letters to Tennyson arranged alphabetically by authors, a list of the contents of the "Red Book" numbers 1 and 2 [Tennyson's manuscripts] a separate list of manuscripts with their destined recipients, and a chronological account of Tennyson's movements up to 1859. The whole is preceded by a list of Tennyson's letters printed in the Memoir. Bound in brown cloth with a dark red spine; lettered on the front cover "Where is it?"
        - Annotations in Mary Emily Prinsep Hichens Tennyson's hand, written in Hallam Tennyson's Alfred Lord Tennyson: A Memoir (London 1897, 2 vols)
          Tipped in are many separate pages and clippings from the proof copy of the Memoir, letters and extracts from Emily Sellwood Tennyson's diary, copied in the hand of Mary Emily Prinsep Hichens Tennyson
          See: Volumes, boxes 11, 12
        - Copies of letters to and from Alfred Tennyson and his wife, originally laid into volumes described above, in Mary Emily Prinsep Hichens Tennyson's hand (Box 6, Folder 334-336)
          Letters were laid into volumes in chronological order, matching the dates in the volumes
        - Notes, extracts from printed works, extracts from Emily Sellwood Tennyson's diary, copied in the hand of Mary Emily Prinsep Hichens Tennyson, from volume one of Alfred Lord Tennyson: A Memoir, [1863], n.d. (Box 6, Folder 337)
        - Notes, extracts from printed works, extracts from Emily Sellwood Tennyson's diary, letters to and from the Tennysons, copied in the hand of Mary Emily Prinsep Hichens Tennyson, from volume two of Alfred Lord Tennyson: A Memoir (Box 6, Folder 338)
          See also: Oversize, box 14, folder 454
        - Annotations (including corrections and additions and extracts from letters) written in the hand of Mary Emily Prinsep Hichens Tennyson in the one volume edition of Hallam Tennyson's book "Alfred Lord Tennyson: A Memoir" (London, 1906) (Box 6, Folder 339-342)
          Volume 1 (the volume is split into two parts corresponding to the volume division in the 1897 edition. Some clippings from the proof copy of the Memoir and copies of letters, etc. in Mary Emily Prinsep Hichens Tennyson's hand are pasted in the volume
        - Annotations (including corrections and additions and extracts from letters) written in the hand of Mary Emily Prinsep Hichens Tennyson in the one volume edition of Hallam Tennyson's book "Alfred Lord Tennyson: A Memoir" (London, 1906) (Box 7, Folder 343-346)
          Volume 2 (the volume is split into two parts corresponding to the volume division in the 1897 edition. Some clippings from the proof copy of the Memoir and copies of letters, etc. in Mary Emily Prinsep Hichens Tennyson's hand are pasted in the volume
        - Printed material, clippings, photographs, and notes in the hand of Mary Prinsep Hichens Tennyson relating to Alfred and Hallam Tennyson removed from volume one of the London 1906 edition of the Memoir (Box 7, Folder 347)
        - Printed material, clippings, copies of letters, and notes in the hand of Mary Prinsep Hichens Tennyson relating to Alfred and Hallam Tennyson removed from volume two of the London 1906 edition of the Memoir (Box 7, Folder 348-352)
        - Notes concerning letters and other material relating to Edward Lear's illustrations for Tennyson's poems (Box 7, Folder 353)
        - Notes on Tennyson, in the hand of Mary Emily Prinsep Tennyson and Hallam Tennyson (Box 7, Folder 354)
        - Copies of letters to and from the Tennysons, extracts from letters and journals about Tennyson, in Mary Emily Prinsep Tennyson's hand (Box 7, Folder 355)
        - Miscellaneous notes, copies of letters, etc. in Mary Emily Prinsep Tennyson and Hallam Tennyson's hand (Box 7, Folder 356-357)
    - Writings of Others
      - Hichens, Andrew. Reminiscences concerning Alfred Lord Tennyson: autograph manuscript (Box 8, Folder 358)
      - Lear, Edward. Autograph manuscript schedule of his landscape drawings to be used as illustrations to specific lines from the poems of Alfred Tennyson (Box 8, Folder 359)
        With a general statement of his aims. The page references in the schedule are to the edition of Tennyson's poems published in two volumes in 1842
  - PRINTED MATERIAL
    - Alfred Tennyson's calling cards, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 360)
    - Emily Sellwood Tennyson's calling cards, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 361)
    - Clipping concerning the "Charge of the Light Brigade," with autograph manuscript note by Alfred Tennyson, 1891 May 2 (Box 8, Folder 362)
      From The Spectator
    - Clippings: Tennyson and his family, 1888-1929 (Box 8, Folder 363-366)
    - Clippings: Tennyson's poetry and reviews of later books, 1848-1911 (Box 8, Folder 367)
    - Clippings: auctions of Tennyson's manuscripts, 1924-28 (Box 8, Folder 368)
    - Clippings: people and places related to Tennyson (Box 8, Folder 369)
    - Commonwealth Prayer. For this Time of the Inauguration of the Commonwealth of Australia, n.d.
      See: Box 7, folder 347
    - Dedication of Tennyson Memorial... Order of Ceremony, [1897] (Box 8, Folder 370)
    - Lines on the Tennyson Beacon, [1897]
      See: Oversize, box 14, folder 455
      See also: Box 7, folder 348
    - Program of Alfred Tennyson's funeral, with a mourner's ticket, [1892] (Box 8, Folder 371)
    - Program of Hallam Tennyson's funeral, [1928]
      See: Box 7, folder 337
    - Prints of Alfred Tennyson, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 372)
    - Rules of the Cosmopolitan Club, and List of Members, 1855 (Box 8, Folder 373)
    - Ticket to the Chapel of St. George, Windsor Castle, [1863]
      See: Box 7, folder 348
  - PHOTOGRAPHS
    - Alfred Tennyson, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 374-375)
    - Bust of Alfred Tennyson by Woolner, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 376-377)
    - Alfred Tennyson and his children (Box 8, Folder 378)
    - Charles Tennyson Turner, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 379)
    - Hallam and Lionel Tennyson (Box 8, Folder 380)
    - Photograph of Hallam Tennyson, n.d.
    - Photograph album containing pictures of Tennyson, his family, and residences, [1879-97]
      See: Oversize, box 16, folder 463
    - Photograph of Farringford, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 381)
    - Postcards of Farringford, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 382)
    - Emily Sellwood Tennyson's grave, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 383)
    - Members of the Tennyson Family, unidentified, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 384-385)
  - OTHER PAPERS
    - Tennyson, Alfred
      - Burgess and Guild Brother Ticket from Kirkwall, 1883 Sep 13 (Box 8, Folder 386)
      - Copy of the Twickenham omnibus schedule, written in Tennyson's hand (Box 8, Folder 387)
      - Cancelled checks made out and signed by Tennyson, 1877-89 (Box 8, Folder 388)
      - Engagement book, April 27-May 10, 1848, with entries for May 3-May 10, 1848 May (Box 8, Folder 389)
        Removed from: Hallam Tennyson's Memoir, London, 1897, vol. 1, p. 275
      - Impressions from his seal, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 390)
      - Invitation to Queen Victoria's ball, 1854 May 17 (Box 9, Folder 391)
      - Lease (fragment) between Mrs. Norwich Cuff and Alfred Tennyson, 1874 Nov 26
        See: Box 7, folder 342
      - Lock of his hair in envelope labelled in Emily Sellwood Tennyson's hand (Box 9, Folder 392)
      - Passport, 1858 Jul 21
        See: Oversize, box 14, folder 457
      - Receipt from the London Library for dues for 1855, 1855 Feb 27
        See: Volumes, box 11
      - Rules [for the admission of visitors to Farringford] with a list of people to be admitted, written in Tennyson's hand (Box 9, Folder 393)
      - Self-portraits: two pen and ink sketches of himself, one in profile, the other full face (Box 9, Folder 394)
        Note on verso in Hallam Tennyson's hand: "Picture of himself"
      - Signatures clipped from letters, with scraps of writings, doodles, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 395-397)
      - "Walking tour in Cornwall and the Scilly Isles," autograph manuscript schedule, 1860 Aug-Sep (Box 9, Folder 398)
        Removed from Hallam Tennyson's Memoir, vol. 1, London
      - Wedding favor, in envelope labelled in Hallam Tennyson's hand (Box 9, Folder 399)
      - Will: the last page of Tennyson's will, 1860 Aug 8 (Box 9, Folder 400)
        Written in a legal hand, with the date written in Tennyson's hand and signed by him; Signed also by George Granville Bradley, and C. M. Bull
    - Tennyson, Hallam
      - Seal given by Hallam Tennyson to the Church of St. Lawrence, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 401)
    - Tennyson, Emily Sellwood
      - Miniature of Miss Sellwood [Emily Sellwood Tennyson?] in watercolor on a thin sheet of ivory, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 402)
        Mounted on an autograph note from Mrs. Fausett to the Misses Bousfield dated Dec 29, 1825. On the wrapper (watermarked 1831) is the following inscription in an unidentified hand: "Miss Sellwood, Horncastle."
    - Other Tennyson Family
      - Catalogue of pictures [sculpture, silver, and other movables] at Farringford, 1911 Oct (Box 9, Folder 403)
        Inventory notebook written in an unidentified hand, with additions and corrections in the hand of Audrey Tennyson, Mary Emily Prinsep Hichens Tennyson, and Hallam Tennyson. A number of letters from various correspondents relating to gifts, etc. are pasted in. Bound in black cloth
      - Coats of Arms of the Tennyson Family, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 404)
        Includes letter from Alfred Scott-Gatty to Hallam Tennyson dated 1883 Dec 28 with drawing of a coat of arms
- Additional Materials, 1820-1912; Series II; 0.2; (1 box)
  Series II, Additional Materials, which consists of other materials acquired from various sources, is organized into three subseries: Correspondence, Writings, and Other Papers. These subseries are arranged by materials belonging to Alfred Tennyson, Hallam Tennyson, and Other Tennyson Family.
  - CORRESPONDENCE
    - Tennyson, Alfred
      - Outgoing
        - 3 ALS to Mrs. Langhorne Burton, London and Cheltenham, Gloucester, [1846-48] (Box 10, Folder 405)
          Purchase, 1954
        - ALS to Frederic Chapman, Richmond, Yorkshire, 1853 Jul 25 (Box 10, Folder 406)
          Gift, 1955
        - ALS to James Thomas Fields, Farringford, Isle of Wight, 1863 Sep 30 (Box 10, Folder 407)
        - ALS (second page only) to Edward FitzGerald, [London], [1847] Apr 21 (Box 10, Folder 407a)
          For first page, see: Box 2, folder 89
        - ALS to Adelaide Kemble, Farringford, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 408)
        - 2 ALS to [Sir James Thomas] Knowles, Farringford, 1870, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 409)
          Dealing with difficulties with his publisher, A. Strahan. Undated letter written at the end of a page containing a copy of a letter from his brother-in-law
        - ALS to [William Allport?] Leighton, Farringford, 1859 Dec 24 (Box 10, Folder 410)
          Purchase, 1949
        - ALS to Edmund L. Lushington, Farringford, 1879 Feb 1 (Box 10, Folder 411)
          Sending a German translation of Harold for correction, and mentioning that he had inserted a few lines in the last scene of the second edition of the play Gift, 1943
        - ALS to Edmund L. Lushington (Box 10, Folder 412)
          Purchase, 1968
        - ALS to Alexander Macmillan, Farringford, Isle of Wight, 1859 Nov 18 (Box 10, Folder 413)
        - ALS to Mr. Macmillan, Farringford, 1868 Jan 8 (Box 10, Folder 414)
        - ALS to [Coventry Kersey Dighton] Patmore, Farringford, [1854 Mar-Apr?] (Box 10, Folder 415)
          Acknowledging Patmore's congratulations [upon the birth of his son, Lionel, on March 16, 1854?] and comments upon his wife's health and local conditions on the Isle of Wight Purchase, 1947
        - ALS to Coventry Patmore, Coniston Water, Ambleside, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 416)
          Gift, 1942
        - ALS and AL to his aunt [Russell], London (Box 10, Folder 417)
          One letter has fragment, signature cut out Purchase, 1974
        - AL (in the third person) to Messrs. Trübner, Haslemere, 1877 Oct 17 (Box 10, Folder 418)
          Probably in the hand of Emily Sellwood Tennyson Purchase
        - ALS to [Queen Victoria], Farringford, 1885 Jul 20 (Box 10, Folder 419)
          Purchase, 1947
        - ALS to [Charles Richard] Weld, Melrose, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 420)
          Gift, 1973
        - ALS to an unidentified recipient, Farringford, 1858 Jun 3 (Box 10, Folder 421)
          Purchase, 1974
        - ALS to an unidentified recipient, Farringford, 1862 Jun 27 (Box 10, Folder 422)
          Gift, 1971
        - ALS to an unidentified recipient, Coniston, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 423)
          Gift, 1970
        - Autograph, clipped from letter, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 424)
    - Tennyson, Hallam
      - ALS to "My Dear Dean" (George Granville Bradley), Isle of Wight, 1889 Dec 29 (Box 10, Folder 425)
        Concerns the funeral of Robert Browning Purchase, 1964
      - ALS to Mrs. Crozien, Farringford, 1912 Jan 24 (Box 10, Folder 426)
      - Autograph note in third person to Mr. Ellis, Haslemere, Surrey, 1879 Sep 14 (Box 10, Folder 427)
      - ALS to Mr. Field, Aldworth, 1884 Aug 16 (Box 10, Folder 428)
        Typewritten copy laid in. The letter refers to Alfred Tennyson Gift, 1942
      - ALS to Emily Tennyson [later Mrs. Jesse], [London], [1832 Jun 2] (Box 10, Folder 429)
        Removed from Erskine, Thomas, The Unconditionsl Freeness of the Gospel in Three Essays. 3rd ed. Edinburgh, 1829. Purchase
      - 2 ALS to his cousin, Farringford, 1894, 1898 (Box 10, Folder 430)
      - ALS to an unidentified recipient, Freshwater, Isle of Wight, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 431)
    - Other Tennyson Family
      - Outgoing
        - Tennyson, Audrey Georgina Florence Boyle Tennyson. ALS to Viscountess [Katharine Frances Scott Hamilton-Russell] Boyne. Haslemere, 1892 Oct 15 (Box 10, Folder 432)
        - Tennyson, Emily Sellwood. 8 ALS to Robert Browning, 1865-89 (Box 10, Folder 433)
          Letter of Dec 19 1872 has ALS by Hallam Tennyson to Robert Browning [Farringford, 19 Dec 1872] on the fourth pagew Gift, 1940
        - Tennyson, Emily Sellwood. ALS to Sir James Thomas Knowles. Haslemere, Surrey, 1871 Nov 21 (Box 10, Folder 434)
        - Tennyson, Frederick. ALS to unidentified bookseller, St. Helier, [1864] Jul 23 (Box 10, Folder 435)
          Purchase, 1957
        - Turner, Charles Tennyson. ALS to John Frere, Somersby, 1830 Jul 27 (Box 10, Folder 436)
          Mentions his father George Clayton Tennyson, his brother Alfred Tennyson, and Arthur Hallam Gift, 1958
        - Turner, Charles Tennyson. ALS to John Frere, Cambridge, 1831 Dec 4 (Box 10, Folder 437)
          Mentions Samuel Coleridge, Arthur Hallam, Alfred and Frederick Tennyson Gift, 1958
        - Turner, Charles Tennyson. ALS to his aunt, Mrs. Russell, Grasby, 1859 Mar 28 (Box 10, Folder 438)
        - Turner, Charles Tennyson. ALS to Frederick Tennyson, Grasby Vicarage, 1865 Jun 13 (Box 10, Folder 439)
  - WRITINGS
    - Tennyson, Alfred
      - "The Coach of Death," autograph manuscript poem, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 440)
        "Mad Tom": autograph manuscript on p. [9-10] Gift, 1954
      - "Dora," autograph manuscript of the last 75 lines of the poem, with corrections, and 16 alternative lines (Box 10, Folder 441)
        Purchase, 1945
      - "England and America in 1782," autograph manuscript of the first stanza only, signed, 1882 Nov 24 (Box 10, Folder 442)
        Accompanied by a photograph of Tennyson signed on verso "A. Tennyson, Easter Day 1882" Gift, 1947
      - Idylls of the King: "Merlin and Vivien": autograph manuscript of lines 6-148 (Box 10, Folder 443)
        Beginning "Whence came she?" Gift, 1947
      - "Locksley Hall," autograph manuscript, signed, 1855 Jan 20 (Box 10, Folder 444)
        On recto of p. 7: "The Golden Year", lines 22-51. Autograph of Frederick Goddard Tuckerman, Farringford, Isle of Wight, Jan. 1855, to whom Tennyson gave the manuscript. Bound in 3/4 morocco and marbled boards, accompanied by clippings from a printed text Gift, 1947
    - Tennyson, Hallam
      - Author's Notes: first proofs, with manuscript corrections, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 445)
        Removed from Alfred Tennyson's In Memoriam London, 1905 Purchase
    - Other Tennyson Family
      - Tennyson, Frederick. "The Poetry of Tennyson, vol. 1, 1820," "The Lyrical Poetry of Tennyson," and "The Prose Writings of Tennyson," each manuscript with a separate title-page, together in an unbound notebook (Box 10, Folder 446-447)
        "The Poetry of Tennyson" dedicated to Miss Lemoine, with drawing of King David with his harp. Text in Latin, titles in English. With photograph of Mrs. Maud M. Ford laid in Gift, 1939
  - OTHER PAPERS
    - Tennyson, Alfred
      - Document signed by Tennyson declaring the loss of 20 share of stock in the Artizans', Labourers' and General Dwellings Co., Haslemere, Surrey, 1887 Sep 24 (Box 10, Folder 448)
        This document is also signed by Ernest Hepburn, a Commissioner of Oaths in the Supreme Court of Judicature in England
    - Tennyson, Hallam
      - Cameron, Julia Margaret Pattle. Photograph of Hallam Tennyson, [1861] (Box 10, Folder 449)
        Purchase, 1989
- Volumes, 0.6; (3 boxes)
  Volumes contains those volumes which did not fit in the previous boxes, but which are not oversize.
  - "Daphne and other Poems": page proofs with autograph ms corrections, 1891 (Box 11, Folder 450)
  - Annotations in Mary Emily Prinsep Hichens Tennyson's hand, written in Hallam Tennyson's Alfred Lord Tennyson: A Memoir (London 1897, 1 of 2 vols) (Box 12, Folder 451)
  - Annotations in Mary Emily Prinsep Hichens Tennyson's hand, written in Hallam Tennyson's Alfred Lord Tennyson: A Memoir (London 1897, 2 of 2 vols) (Box 13, Folder 452)
- Oversize, 3.4; (2 boxes)
  Oversize contains material from Series I, arranged in box order.
  - "Queen Mary," galley proof of a portion of Act IV, Scene 3, with autograph manuscript corrections (from Series I), n.d. (Box 14, Folder 453)
    Two copies.
  - Notes, extracts from printed works, extracts from Emily Sellwood Tennyson's diary, letters to and from the Tennysons, copied in the hand of Mary Emily Prinsep Hichens Tennyson, from volume two of Alfred Lord Tennyson: A Memoir (from Series I) (Box 14, Folder 454)
  - Lines on the Tennyson Beacon (from Series I), [1897] (Box 14, Folder 455)
    See also: Box 7, folder 339
  - Empty folder (Box 14, Folder 456)
  - Passport (from Series I), 1858 Jul 21 (Box 14, Folder 457)
  - Photograph album containing pictures of Tennyson, his family, and residences (from Series I), [1879-97] (Box 16, Folder 463)
- Restricted Fragile
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted fragile material. Reference surrogates have been substituted in the main files. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
  - Box 1, folders 15, 25 (Box 15, Folder 458)
  - Box 3, folder 169, 173 (Box 15, Folder 459)
  - Box 5, folder 328 (Box 15, Folder 460)
  - Box 8, folders 363, 367-368 (Box 15, Folder 461)
  - Box 8, folders 363, 367-368 (Box bsd, folder 462)